Is it easy to get there?
行きやすいの?
Hmm, maybe.
う ーん、かもしれない
Then I still have to go, come.
そしたらまだ行ってもん、来
stomach.
い
Come out.
出 て
Then, while I was guessing, I guessed it myself and had to be patient.
そしたらさ、当てながらさ、自分で当てて我慢して
Don't go until I tell you.
俺が言ってまで行っちゃダメだよ
I'm going.
行っちゃう
Be patient, here.
我慢して、ほら
No, no, no.
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ
Are you going?
行っちゃうの?
Did you ask for it?
頼んできた?
Have you gone?
行っちゃったの?
Well then, let's go, then.
じゃあ行っちゃおう、じゃあ
It's easy to get to.
行きやすいんだね
It's ticklish.
くすぐったいもん
くすぐったいもんだ
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫だ、大丈夫だ
Is this okay?
こっちは大丈夫?
It's okay here.
こっちは大丈夫
Isn't it easy to get there?
行きやすいんじゃない?
Hmm, maybe so.
うーん、そうかもしれない
I'm going.
行っちゃう
It's been a while.
久しぶりだから
久 しぶりなんだ
yes.
はい
eye
め
I can smell it.
っちゃ 匂い嗅いでるね
I quite like the smell.
結構匂い好きなんだ
I kind of like it.
なんか、好きです
I like it.
好きだな
Do you have a favorite penis shape?
なんかちんこの好きな形とかあったりするの?
Length and cap.
長さとかさ
I like the bigger ones.
大きいのがいいです
How many points is this?
これ何点くらい?
How many points?
何点くらい?
何点くらいかな?
Then take a picture on camera.
じゃあカメラに撮って
6 o'clock.
6点
There are many points in this.
何点もあってんじゃんこれ
It's worth 10 points.
10点もあってんじゃん
It's in the middle.
中間ですね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
it's okay.
大丈夫 です
Seriously, try touching it.
マジで触ってみて
Eat
食べて
Look.
み て
cold.
寒い
Try moving yourself.
自分で動いてみて
Feels good.
気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいね
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Here.
ここ ね
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい、ごめんなさい